{
    "id": "008cbda4b1b4422c8bb3d25a2e0f2a62",
    "title": "Many and many of",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6f8586141ec449b69fcd1fce3bdae5d8",
            "title": "Many And Many Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………… families own more than one vehicle these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................... us are disappointed with the government’s economic policies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. them are late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There weren’t ………………… students in the class.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ..................... you have submitted your assignments?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has got ……………….. friends in the city.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… them are not interested in the offer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There aren’t ………………… apples on the tree.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ………………… people were there?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… those who participated in the program said that they enjoyed it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}